<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Productivity on Synappse | Web &amp; Mobile Solutions</title>
    <link>https://synappse.co/categories/productivity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Productivity on Synappse | Web &amp; Mobile Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://synappse.co/categories/productivity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Estimote hackathon</title>
      <link>https://synappse.co/blog/estimote-hackathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://synappse.co/blog/estimote-hackathon/</guid>
      <description>On Saturday (November 30, 2013) had place a first of the series of preparation hackathons for the Jitter hackathon at Mobile Central Europe conference. The Synappse Team went there to participate and make friends with this hackathon partner – Estimote.
Task The idea was to get familiar with iBeacons technology which is why Estimote prepared some presentation and had someone on the side to help with technical issues.
The target for us was to implement iBeacon region monitoring into our app Neon Muzeum which was sent to the App Store review another day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlimited vacation vs Productivity</title>
      <link>https://synappse.co/blog/work-perks-unlimited-vacation-vs-productivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://synappse.co/blog/work-perks-unlimited-vacation-vs-productivity/</guid>
      <description>There is a tenuous balance that every business organization must face—a positive and relaxing work culture and the need to maximize productivity. Some companies, particularly the more established ones, tend to forego developing a positive work culture altogether and simply expect employees to be the henchmen of the management’s will. This state of affairs is naturally demotivating and these companies have seen a dip in their productivity related to that. Now that even the most ardent Old School businessmen and women are coming to grips with the benefits of a positive work culture, they are left with the challenge of figuring out how to design a maximally productive one.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
