<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>iBeacons on Synappse | Web &amp; Mobile Solutions</title>
    <link>https://synappse.co/categories/ibeacons/</link>
    <description>Recent content in iBeacons on Synappse | Web &amp; Mobile Solutions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://synappse.co/categories/ibeacons/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>iBeacons in Retail</title>
      <link>https://synappse.co/blog/ibeacons-in-retail/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://synappse.co/blog/ibeacons-in-retail/</guid>
      <description>iBeacons is that kind of technology that you have probably heard a lot but haven&amp;rsquo;t seen it in the real world at all. But there are many applications out there and in most cases, the majority of benefits are presented to people at the other end.
Every time you feel that you are guided inside buildings or it seems that you got super personalized, location-aware and just-in-time notification or suggestion in the app - you probably are looking at the effects of the iBeacons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Estimote hackathon</title>
      <link>https://synappse.co/blog/estimote-hackathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://synappse.co/blog/estimote-hackathon/</guid>
      <description>On Saturday (November 30, 2013) had place a first of the series of preparation hackathons for the Jitter hackathon at Mobile Central Europe conference. The Synappse Team went there to participate and make friends with this hackathon partner – Estimote.
Task The idea was to get familiar with iBeacons technology which is why Estimote prepared some presentation and had someone on the side to help with technical issues.
The target for us was to implement iBeacon region monitoring into our app Neon Muzeum which was sent to the App Store review another day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UPC Think Big Final Gala 2014</title>
      <link>https://synappse.co/blog/upc-think-big-final-gala-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://synappse.co/blog/upc-think-big-final-gala-2014/</guid>
      <description>On the 22nd of the January, we have been a part UPC Think Big final gala which featured 10 of the contest finalists. We&amp;rsquo;ve been given an opportunity to bring closer our idea to the judges and answer their questions after 3min pitch.
Unfortunately we didn&amp;rsquo;t win but we had a great occasion to test our presentation skills and to check if this particular audience will know more about iBeacon technology - the answer apparently is not so much, more and more people start to know something or just they heard about Estimote company but still the understanding of iBeacons technology is very basic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HACKWAW - quantified self hackathon</title>
      <link>https://synappse.co/blog/hackwaw-quantified-self-hackathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://synappse.co/blog/hackwaw-quantified-self-hackathon/</guid>
      <description>Just a short note about my last weekend. I spent a great time at HACKWAW hackathon focused on Quantified Self movement. That was an amazing opportunity to met people not only from the tech industry but also to chat with mentors from the science world.
That was a truly amazing event — so many creative people, ideas and&amp;hellip; gadgets of course! The venue was fantastic, organizers did a great job. Ola, Kuba kudos for you!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
